Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ vanessajovana (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Content Design
Content Marketing
Microcopy

Certifications

Microsoft Office Specialist: Word Associate (Office 2019)

Startup Campus Batch 4 - UI/UX Design

PMI Project Management Ready™

Honors-Awards

Winner, Ambassadors of UPH Medan Campus 2021

Champion, English Speech Competition

1st Runner-up, English Newscasting Competition

Winner, Ambassador of ONE UPH 2021

1st Runner-up, UI/UX Competition

Vanessa Jovana

UX Writer at Topremit • Freelance Content Writer & Content Specialist

Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Summary

A highly-motivated and enthusiastic 4th year Information Systems student at Pelita Harapan University, who is actively involved in organizations and competitions, which have successfully sharpened leadership, time-management, public speaking, and design skills. Love to learn and experience new things, especially something out-of-the-box.

Experience

Topremit
UX Writer
September 2023 - Present (6 months)

Lasence Bakeshop Content Specialist June 2023 - Present (9 months)

FAIV Agency Co-Founder November 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months) Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Elena Lingerie Content Specialist March 2023 - September 2023 (7 months) Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Universitas Pelita Harapan

2 years 1 month

Advisor of Ambassadors of Universitas Pelita Harapan Medan Campus 2022

August 2022 - August 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Guest Speaker at Ambassadors of UPH's Talk Show: Beyond The Limits

January 2023 - January 2023 (1 month)

Head of Ambassadors of Universitas Pelita Harapan Medan Campus 2021/2022

August 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Vice Coordinator of Public Speaking Club

August 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Guest Speaker in Ambassadors of UPH's Talk Show: Understand The Wonderful You

January 2022 - January 2022 (1 month)

Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Winner of Ambassadors of Universitas Pelita Harapan Medan Campus 2021

August 2021 - August 2021 (1 month)

Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Majelis Perwakilan Mahasiswa Universitas Pelita Harapan Member of Public Relations Commission August 2022 - August 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Indonesian International Student Mobility Awards 5 months

Head of Copywriter Division | IISMA 2022 Yearbook September 2022 - December 2022 (4 months)

Nanyang Technological University Singapore Awardee August 2022 - December 2022 (5 months)

Singapore, Singapore

Over 7.501 participants, 1.155 awardees were chosen and spread out in different host universities and countries.

Head of Event Division | Tales From Around The World (Asia Region) September 2022 - November 2022 (3 months)

Badan Eksekutif Mahasiswa Universitas Pelita Harapan President

August 2021 - August 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Page 2 of 3

National Public Speaking Competition UPHMC Head of Design Department July 2021 - November 2021 (5 months)

PrimeOne School's Student Council 2 years 1 month

President August 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 1 month) Kota Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Vice Treasurer August 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 1 month) Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Prime One School
Ms. PrimeOne School
March 2017 - March 2018 (1 year 1 month)
Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Education

Universitas Pelita Harapan

Bachelor's degree, Management Information Systems, General (2020 - 2024)

Startup Campus

UI/UX Design · (February 2023 - June 2023)

Nanyang Technological University Singapore Non-graduating, School of Computer Science and Engineering · (August 2022 - December 2022)

PrimeOne School Medan High School, Science · (2011 - 2020)

Kenni Khoza Fashion Design Centre Fashion/Apparel Design · (May 2021)